Guide to the Al Swift Congressional Papers 1885-2003
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
- Project Files, 1965-1995; Series IX
  - Scott Johnson, 1972-1987; Subseries 8
    - Broadcast Deregulation
      - Hearing on Options for Cable Legislation, 1983 (Box-folder 525/3)
      - Must Carry Task Force Meeting, 1983 (Box-folder 525/4)
      - Syndication Ruling, 1983 (Box-folder 525/5)
      - Syndication Ruling, 1983 (Box-folder 525/6)
    - Cross Ownership, 1980 (Box-folder 525/7)
    - Cross Ownership, 1980 (Box-folder 525/8)
    - Cross Ownership, 1980 (Box-folder 525/9)
    - Cross Ownership, 1980 (Box-folder 525/10)
    - Cross Ownership, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 526/1)
    - Cross Ownership, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 526/2)
    - Cross Ownership, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 526/3)
    - Cross Ownership, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 526/4)
    - Cross Ownership, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 526/5)
    - Direct Broadcast Satellites, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 526/6)
    - Direct Broadcast Satellites, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 526/7)
    - Direct Broadcast Satellites, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 526/8)
    - Direct Broadcast Satellites, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 526/9)
    - Direct Broadcast Satellites, 1981 (Box-folder 527/1)
    - Direct Broadcast Satellites, 1981 (Box-folder 527/2)
    - Helium, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 527/3)
    - Helium, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 527/4)
    - Helium, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 527/5)
    - Helium, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 527/6)
    - Helium, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 528/1)
    - Helium, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 528/2)
    - Helium, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 528/3)
    - Helium, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 528/4)
    - Presidential Primary Proposals, 1972-1981 (Box-folder 528/5)
    - Public Broadcasting, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 528/6)
    - Public Broadcasting, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 528/7)
    - Public Broadcasting, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 528/8)
    - Public Broadcasting, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 529/1)
    - Public Broadcasting, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 529/2)
    - Public Broadcasting, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 529/3)
    - Public Broadcasting, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 529/4)
    - Public Broadcasting, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 529/5)
    - Public Broadcasting, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 529/6)
    - Public Broadcasting, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 529/7)
    - Public Broadcasting, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 530/1)
    - Public Broadcasting, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 530/2)
    - Public Broadcasting, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 530/3)
    - Public Broadcasting, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 530/4)
    - Radio, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 530/5)
    - Radio, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 530/6)
    - Radio, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 531/1)
    - Radio, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 531/2)
    - Regulatory Council for Legislation, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 531/3)
    - Regulatory Council for Legislation, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 531/4)
    - Satellite
      - Alternative International Satellite Systems, 1984 (Box-folder 531/5)
      - Communications Network for American Indian Populations, 1983 (Box-folder 531/6)
      - Encryption Satellite Communications Bill, 1987 (Box-folder 531/7)
      - Initiative for Trans-Atlantic Satellite Facilities, 1984 (Box-folder 531/8)
      - Intelstat Bill, 1985 (Box-folder 531/9)
      - Intelstat Bill, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 532/1)
      - Intelstat Bill, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 532/2)
      - Intelstat Bill, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 532/3)
      - Intelstat Bill, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 532/4)
      - Intelstat Bill, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 532/5)
      - Intelstat Bill, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 533/1)
      - Intelstat Bill, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 533/2)
      - Intelstat Bill, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 533/3)
      - Intelstat Bill, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 533/4)
      - Intelstat Bill, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 533/5)
      - Intelstat Bill, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 533/6)
      - Intelstat Bill, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 534/1)
      - Intelstat Bill, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 534/2)
      - Intelstat Bill, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 534/3)
      - Intelstat Bill, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 534/4)
      - Intelstat Bill, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 534/5)
      - Intelstat Bill, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 535/1)
      - Intelstat Bill, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 535/2)
      - Intelstat Bill, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 535/3)
      - Intelstat Bill, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 535/4)
      - Rural Satellite Dish Owners Protection Act, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 535/5)
      - Rural Satellite Dish Owners Protection Act, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 535/6)
      - Satellite Dishes and Scrambling Issues, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 536/1)
      - Satellite Piracy, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 536/2)
      - Satellite Piracy, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 536/3)
      - Satellite Television Programming Access Act, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 536/4)
      - Satellite Television Programming Access Act, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 536/5)
      - Satellite Television Programming Access Act, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 536/6)
    - Section 222 Repeal, 1981 (Box-folder 536/7)
    - Section 222 Repeal, 1981 (Box-folder 537/1)
    - Telecommunications
      - Broadcasting, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 537/2)
      - Broadcasting, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 537/3)
      - Broadcasting, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 537/4)
      - Broadcasting, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 537/5)
      - Broadcasting, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 537/6)
      - Broadcasting, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 537/7)
      - Broadcasting, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 537/8)
      - Broadcasting, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 537/9)
      - Broadcasting, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 537/10)
      - Broadcasting, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 538/1)
      - Broadcasting, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 538/2)
      - Broadcasting, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 538/3)
      - Business Restrictions on Bell Operating Companies, 1987 (Box-folder 538/4)
      - Canadian-U.S. Communications Conference, 1983 (Box-folder 538/5)
      - Cougar Mountain Radiation Levels, 1985 (Box-folder 538/6)
      - Communications Technical Amendment Act, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 538/7)
      - Communications Technical Amendment Act, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 538/8)
      - Communications Technical Amendment Act, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 538/9)
      - Communications Technical Amendment Act, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 538/10)
      - Communications Technical Amendment Act, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 538/11)
      - Communications Technical Amendment Act, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 539/1)
      - Communications Technical Amendment Act, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 539/2)
      - Corporate Takeovers and Mergers, 1985 (Box-folder 539/3)
      - Corporate Takeovers and Mergers, 1985 (Box-folder 539/4)
      - Corporate Takeovers and Mergers, 1985 (Box-folder 539/5)
      - Electronic Monitoring Bill, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 539/6)
      - Federal Communications Commission Authorization, 1981 (Box-folder 539/7)
      - Federal Communications Commission Fee Schedule, 1985 (Box-folder 539/8)
      - Federal Communications Commission Oversight Hearings, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 539/9)
      - Federal Communications Commission Oversight Hearings, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 539/10)
      - General, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 540/1)
      - General, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 540/2)
      - General, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 540/3)
      - General, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 540/4)
      - General, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 540/5)
      - Grove City Bill, 1987 (Box-folder 540/6)
      - House Resolution 3131, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 540/7)
      - House Resolution 3131, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 540/8)
      - House Resolution 3131, 1987 (Box-folder 541/1)
      - National Public Radio, 1987 (Box-folder 541/2)
      - National Technological University, 1987 (Box-folder 541/3)
      - Radio Marti, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 541/4)
      - Radio Marti, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 541/5)
      - Radio Marti, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 541/6)
      - Radio Marti, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 541/7)
      - Radio Marti, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 541/8)
      - Radio Marti, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 541/9)
      - Radio Marti, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 542/1)
      - Radio Marti, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 542/2)
      - Radio Marti, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 542/3)
      - Radio Marti, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 542/4)
      - Radio Marti, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 542/5)
      - Subcommittee People, 1984 (Box-folder 542/6)
      - Teleport Communications, 1987 (Box-folder 542/7)
    - Telephone
      - AT&T and Pacific Northwest Bell, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 542/8)
      - AT&T and Pacific Northwest Bell, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 542/9)
      - AT&T and Pacific Northwest Bell, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 543/1)
      - AT&T and Pacific Northwest Bell, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 543/2)
      - AT&T and Pacific Northwest Bell, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 543/3)
      - AT&T and Pacific Northwest Bell, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 543/4)
      - AT&T and Pacific Northwest Bell, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 543/5)
      - AT&T and Pacific Northwest Bell, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 543/6)
      - AT&T and Pacific Northwest Bell, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 543/7)
      - AT&T and Pacific Northwest Bell, 1983 (Box-folder 544/1)
      - AT&T and Pacific Northwest Bell, 1983 (Box-folder 544/2)
      - AT&T and Pacific Northwest Bell, 1983 (Box-folder 544/3)
      - AT&T and Pacific Northwest Bell, 1983 (Box-folder 544/4)
      - AT&T and Pacific Northwest Bell, 1983 (Box-folder 544/5)
      - AT&T and Pacific Northwest Bell, 1983 (Box-folder 544/6)
      - AT&T and Pacific Northwest Bell, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 545/1)
      - AT&T and Pacific Northwest Bell, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 545/2)
      - AT&T Consent Decree/ House Resolution 3800, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 545/3)
      - AT&T Consent Decree/ House Resolution 3800, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 545/4)
      - AT&T Consent Decree/ House Resolution 3800, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 545/5)
      - AT&T Consent Decree/ House Resolution 3800, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 546/1)
      - AT&T Consent Decree/ House Resolution 3800, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 546/2)
      - AT&T Consent Decree/ House Resolution 3800, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 546/3)
      - AT&T Consent Decree/ House Resolution 3800, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 546/4)
      - AT&T Consent Decree/ House Resolution 3800, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 546/5)
      - AT&T Consent Decree/ House Resolution 3800, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 546/6)
      - AT&T Consent Decree/ House Resolution 3800, 1986 (Box-folder 547/1)
      - AT&T Consent Decree/ House Resolution 3800, 1986 (Box-folder 547/2)
      - AT&T Consent Decree/ House Resolution 3800, 1986 (Box-folder 547/3)
      - AT&T Consent Decree/ House Resolution 3800, 1986 (Box-folder 547/4)
      - AT&T Consent Decree/ House Resolution 3800, 1986 (Box-folder 547/5)
      - AT&T Consent Decree/ House Resolution 3800, 1986 (Box-folder 547/6)
      - AT&T Consent Decree/ House Resolution 3800, 1986 (Box-folder 547/7)
      - AT&T Consent Decree/ House Resolution 3800, 1986 (Box-folder 548/1)
      - AT&T Consent Decree/ House Resolution 3800, 1986 (Box-folder 548/2)
      - AT&T Consent Decree/ House Resolution 3800, 1986 (Box-folder 548/3)
      - AT&T Consent Decree/ House Resolution 3800, 1986 (Box-folder 548/4)
      - Bypass Issue, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 548/5)
      - Common Carrier Bill/ House Resolution 6121, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 548/6)
      - Common Carrier Bill/ House Resolution 6121, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 548/7)
      - Common Carrier Bill/ House Resolution 6121, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 549/1)
      - Common Carrier Bill/ House Resolution 6121, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 549/2)
      - Common Carrier Bill/ House Resolution 6121, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 549/3)
      - Common Carrier Bill/ House Resolution 6121, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 549/4)
      - Common Carrier Bill/ House Resolution 6121, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 549/5)
      - Common Carrier Bill/ House Resolution 6121, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 549/6)
      - Common Carrier Bill/ House Resolution 6121, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 550/1)
      - Common Carrier Bill/ House Resolution 6121, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 550/2)
      - Common Carrier Bill/ House Resolution 6121, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 550/3)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 550/4)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 550/5)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 550/6)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 550/7)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 551/1)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 551/2)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 551/3)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 551/4)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 551/5)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 551/6)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 552/1)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 552/2)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 552/3)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 552/4)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 552/5)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 552/6)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 552/7)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1986 (Box-folder 553/1)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1986 (Box-folder 553/2)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1986 (Box-folder 553/3)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1986 (Box-folder 553/4)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1986 (Box-folder 553/5)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1986 (Box-folder 553/6)
      - Deregulation of AT&T, 1986 (Box-folder 553/7)
      - General, 1982 (Box-folder 553/8)
      - Syndication Ruling, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 553/9)
      - Syndication Ruling, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 554/1)
      - Syndication Ruling, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 554/2)
      - Syndication Ruling, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 554/3)
      - Syndication Ruling, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 554/4)
      - Syndication Ruling, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 554/5)
      - Syndication Ruling, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 555/1)
      - Syndication Ruling, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 555/2)
      - Syndication Ruling, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 555/3)
      - Syndication Ruling, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 555/4)
      - Syndication Ruling, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 555/5)
      - Syndication Ruling, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 555/6)
      - Syndication Ruling, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 556/1)
      - Syndication Ruling, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 556/2)
      - Syndication Ruling, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 556/3)
      - Syndication Ruling, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 556/4)
      - Syndication Ruling, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 556/5)
      - Syndication Ruling, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 556/6)
      - Syndication Ruling, 1984 (Box-folder 557/1)
      - Telecommunications Act of 1982/ House Resolution 5158, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 557/2)
      - Telecommunications Act of 1982/ House Resolution 5158, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 557/3)
      - Telecommunications Act of 1982/ House Resolution 5158, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 557/4)
      - Telecommunications Act of 1982/ House Resolution 5158, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 557/5)
      - Telecommunications Act of 1982/ House Resolution 5158, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 557/6)
      - Telecommunications Act of 1982/ House Resolution 5158, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 557/7)
      - Telecommunications Act/ House Resolution 5158, 1982 (Box-folder 558/1)
      - Telecommunications Act/ House Resolution 5158, 1982 (Box-folder 558/2)
      - Telecommunications Act/ House Resolution 5158, 1982 (Box-folder 558/3)
      - Telecommunications Act/ House Resolution 5158, 1982 (Box-folder 558/4)
      - Telecommunications Reform Act/ Senate Bill 898, 1981 (Box-folder 558/5)
      - Telecommunications Reform Act/ Senate Bill 898, 1981 (Box-folder 558/6)
      - Telecommunications Employees Protection Act, 1981 (Box-folder 558/7)
      - Universal Phone Service Bills, 1983 (Box-folder 558/8)
      - Universal Phone Service Bills, 1983 (Box-folder 559/1)
      - Universal Phone Service Bills, 1983 (Box-folder 559/2)
      - Universal Phone Service Bills, 1983 (Box-folder 559/3)
      - Universal Phone Service Bills, 1983 (Box-folder 559/4)
      - Universal Phone Service Bills, 1983 (Box-folder 559/5)
      - Universal Phone Service Bills, 1983 (Box-folder 559/6)
      - Universal Phone Service Bills, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 560/1)
      - Universal Phone Service Bills, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 560/2)
      - Universal Phone Service Bills, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 560/3)
      - Universal Phone Service Bills, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 560/4)
      - Universal Phone Service Bills, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 560/5)
      - Universal Phone Service Bills, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 560/6)
      - Universal Phone Service Bills, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 560/7)
      - Universal Phone Service Bills, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 561/1)
      - Universal Phone Service Bills, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 561/2)
      - Universal Phone Service Bills, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 561/3)
      - Universal Phone Service Bills, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 561/4)
      - Universal Phone Service Bills, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 561/5)
    - Television, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 561/6)
    - Television, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 561/7)
    - Television, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 562/1)
    - Television, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 562/2)
    - Television, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 562/3)
    - Television, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 562/4)
    - Television, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 562/5)
    - Television, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 562/6)
  - Matt Krieger, 1991-1994; Subseries 9
    Note: Includes projects related to Northwest Straits Marine Sanctuary, Piazza Construction, taxation revenue estimates, and wetlands.
    - Northwest Straits Marine Sanctuary, 1994 (Box-folder 563/1)
    - Piazza Construction, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 563/2)
    - Swift Bill Listing for 96th Congress, Undated (Box-folder 563/3)
    - Taxation Revenue Estimates, 1991 (Box-folder 563/4)
    - Wetlands, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 563/5)
    - Wetlands, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 563/6)
    - Wetlands, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 563/7)
    - Wetlands, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 563/8)
    - Wetlands, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 563/9)
    - Wetlands, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 563/10)
    - Wetlands, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 563/11)
    - Wetlands, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 563/12)
  - Steve McBee, 1986-1994; Subseries 10
    Note: Includes projects related to defense issues including the Whidbey Naval Air Station and the Everett Homeport.
    - Candidates Forum, 1992 (Box-folder 564/1)
    - Defense Issues-Aspin's Annual Report, 1994 (Box-folder 564/2)
    - Defense Issues-Base Closure and Realignment, 1991 (Box-folder 564/3)
    - Defense Issues-Base Closure and Realignment, 1991 (Box-folder 564/4)
    - Defense Issues-Base Closure and Realignment, 1991 (Box-folder 564/5)
    - Defense Issues-Base Closure and Realignment, 1991 (Box-folder 564/6)
    - Defense Issues-Base Closure and Realignment, 1991 (Box-folder 564/7)
    - Defense Issues-Base Closure and Realignment, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 565/1)
    - Defense Issues-Base Closure and Realignment, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 565/2)
    - Defense Issues-Base Closure and Realignment, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 565/3)
    - Defense Issues-Base Closure and Realignment, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 565/4)
    - Defense Issues-Base Closure and Realignment, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 565/5)
    - Defense Issues-General, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 565/6)
    - Defense Issues-General, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 566/1)
    - Defense Issues-General, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 566/2)
    - Defense Issues-General, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 566/3)
    - Defense Issues-General, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 566/4)
    - Everett Homeport, 1988-1993 (Box-folder 566/5)
    - Everett Homeport, 1988-1993 (Box-folder 566/6)
    - Everett Homeport, 1988-1993 (Box-folder 566/7)
    - Everett Homeport - General, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 567/1)
    - Everett Homeport - Tulalip Reservation Site, 1992 (Box-folder 567/2)
    - Naval Air Station Whidbey Island
      - Closure - Community Effects, 1991 (Box-folder 567/3)
      - Closure - Community Response, 1991 (Box-folder 567/4)
      - Closure - Externalities, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 567/5)
      - Closure - Facts and Figures, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 567/6)
      - Closure - Facts and Figures, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 567/7)
      - Closure - Facts and Figures, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 567/8)
      - Closure - General Work, 1991 (Box-folder 567/9)
      - Closure - Official Facts and Figures, 1991 (Box-folder 568/1)
      - Closure - Press/Official Documents, 1991 (Box-folder 568/2)
      - Commercial Activities Program, 1988 (Box-folder 568/3)
      - "Contracting-Out", 1986 (Box-folder 568/4)
      - General, 1985 (Box-folder 568/5)
      - General, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 568/6)
      - General, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 568/7)
      - General, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 568/8)
      - General, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 569/1)
      - Noise Issue, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 569/2)
      - Noise Issue, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 569/3)
      - Noise Issue, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 569/4)
    - National Treasury Employees Union Report, 1988 (Box-folder 569/5)
    - State Department - Phone Directory, 1989 (Box-folder 569/6)
    - State Department - Treaties in Force, 1993 (Box-folder 569/7)
  - Eric Niles, 1987-1993; Subseries 11
    Note: Includes projects related the the Earthquake Insurance Bill and the Elwha Dam.
    - Earthquake Insurance Bill, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 570/1)
    - Earthquake Insurance Bill, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 570/2)
    - Earthquake Insurance Bill, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 570/3)
    - Earthquake Insurance Bill, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 570/4)
    - Earthquake Insurance Bill, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 570/5)
    - Earthquake Insurance Bill, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 570/6)
    - Earthquake Insurance Bill - Earthquake Hearing Testimony, 1992 (Box-folder 571/1)
    - Elwha Dam
      - Address/Telephone Lists, 1992 (Box-folder 571/2)
      - Appropriations, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 571/3)
      - Background Notes, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 571/4)
      - Briefing By Elwha Tribe, 1993 (Box-folder 571/5)
      - Dam Removal and Sediment Management, 1991 (Box-folder 571/6)
      - Dam Removal and Sediment Management, 1991 (Box-folder 571/7)
      - Daishowa Compromise Proposal, 1992 (Box-folder 571/8)
      - Daishowa Info/Studies, 1989 (Box-folder 571/9)
      - Daishowa Power Interests, 1991 (Box-folder 571/10)
      - Daishowa Paper Mill Press, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 571/11)
      - Draft Correspondence H.R.4844, Undated (Box-folder 571/12)
      - Elwha Hearing, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 572/1)
      - Energy & Commerce Correspondence, 1992 (Box-folder 572/2)
      - FERC Relicensing, 1991 (Box-folder 572/3)
      - House Testimony, 1992 (Box-folder 572/4)
      - Bill - H.R.4844, 1992 (Box-folder 572/5)
      - H.R.4844 Drafts, 1992 (Box-folder 572/6)
      - Impact Assessment, 1987 (Box-folder 572/7)
      - Investigative Request, 1989 (Box-folder 572/8)
      - James River II, Inc., 1989 (Box-folder 573/1)
      - Legal Issue Analysis, 1990 (Box-folder 573/2)
      - Meetings Notes, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 573/3)
      - Petition for Review, 1992 (Box-folder 573/4)
      - Port Angeles Correspondence, 1992 (Box-folder 573/5)
      - Press, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 573/6)
      - Publications, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 573/7)
      - Restoration Act, 1992 (Box-folder 573/8)
      - Restoration Act Correspondence, 1992 (Box-folder 573/9)
      - Elwha Dam, 1989-1993 (Box-folder 573/10)
        (missing)
      - Return Letters, Undated (Box-folder 573/11)
      - S 2527 Drafts, 1992 (Box-folder 573/12)
      - S 2527 Hearing, 1992 (Box-folder 574/1)
      - S 2527 Hearing, 1992 (Box-folder 547/2)
  - Midori Okazaki, 1978-1992; Subseries 12
    Note: Includes projects related to the Department of Energy; the Elwha Dam, environmental compliance; and fossil fuels.
    - Department of Energy Safety Advisory Committee, 1988 (Box-folder 575/1)
    - Elwha Dams
      - Analysis of Legal Issues Concerning the Licensing of the Elwha Project and the Glines Canyon Project, 1990 (Box-folder 575/2)
      - Background, 1989 (Box-folder 575/3)
      - Clean Air Act Amendments, 1990 (Box-folder 575/4)
      - Correspondence - Department of Energy, 1990 (Box-folder 575/5)
      - Concerns and Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 575/6)